I hope the taste of peach is not so
sweet as to say,
It's sweet, you!
Good morning!
Today,
I think it's better to ask you where
you are.
Yes!
This time, I'm in Kourimachi,
Fukushima!
Yay!
Good morning!
Welcome!
Today,
we are going to play in Kourimachi.
Yay!
There is someone who can guide you.
Can you call him?
Yes!
Mr. Okazaki!
Hello!
Thank you for coming today!
I'm Okazaki, the actor of Kourimachi.
Kourimachi is
full of fun and
delicious food.
Let's go there
with everyone!
It's funny!
Today,
we have another guide.
Ready?
It's Hotapi!
Hotapi!
It's cute!
This is a hint of a fun trip.
Let's think about it and go!
Let's go to the next place!
Let's go!
We are here!
This is
a place where
you can exchange food and brain.
It's called Kouri in Riga.
Thank you for watching! Please
subscribe to our channel!
And today, I'm going to make a
pizza experience in my heart.
Thank you.
Then, I used that peach immediately.
I said it.
It's nothing.
Let's make a pizza like that.
I'll make it.
Yeah!
I'm going to have a pizza making
experience from now on.
Yeah!
I would like to invite the staff who
will guide me.
Honda-san of the pizza staff.
Thank you.
Please come in.
The lineup looks like this.
Great!
Thank you for watching.
This is the cream box of Fukushima.
What?
It's great.
It's a dessert pizza.
I see.
We are going to make pizza without
eating any snack.
Yes, of course.
Have you ever made pizza?
No.
I have made pizza once.
Wow.
Do you know how to make it?
No.
Let's make pizza one by one.
Yes.
The name of this pizza is Napoli pizza.
It emphasizes ears.
Push the middle part.
Napoli pizza.
It's stretching.
It's going to be torn.
It's turning.
Is it turning?
I want to see it.
It's amazing.
It's perfect.
Let's go.
I want to sleep with this.
It's really fluffy.
I'm not good at it.
It's difficult.
Can you turn it?
I'll try.
I can smell the incident.
I'll stop.
Please edit it.
It's harder than I thought.
She is good at it.
Did you finish?
I finished.
I'll give you some points for each part
of your elbow.
No way!
You should say it first.
I'll give you 10 points.
7 points.
I'll get 8 points.
You have beautiful ears.
I'm not good at this.
You have a thin ear.
7 points.
We all got the same score.
We got 23 points.
You have beautiful ears.
What are you going to do next?
I'll prepare the ingredients.
Yeah, I prepared the ingredients.
I had a spoon there, so thank you.
Is it okay?
It's a high-class snack.
Are you ready for a snack?
Yes.
I'm good at it.
I'll enjoy it.
Itadakimasu
It's delicious
It's sweet
It's really delicious
Itadakimasu
It's so good.
It's so sweet.
Now, we have finished tasting the
cream.
We are going to make 7pizza.
7pizza.
I'll make my pizza.
It's a pizza.
It's a sweet mochi.
What about Miu-gon?
What should I do with Miu-gon?
I'll put the ingredients first.
OK.
I'll try it.
I'll put the ingredients on the pizza.
I'll put bacon on it.
I'm curious about the peach.
Peach and cream box.
I'll put the peach on it.
I want to make a face here.
You're making a face.
I can't find the peach.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Please use it well.
I want to eat it.
It's good.
Wait.
You can't eat it.
I put this on the pizza.
It's done.
Wow.
We just need to bake it.
Do you have a name for the pizza?
Wait a minute.
I'll call you.
What kind of pizza is yours?
Honda pizza.
Simple Honda pizza.
It's good.
Please subscribe to my channel.
Thank you for your viewing.
Rui-chan, Rungelito.
Rungelito is cute.
Rungelito.
Who is your favorite character?
I like Honda Takeru.
Takeru?
I like him.
Please subscribe to my channel.
What is the most popular word in the
world?
Um...
Gyaru no...
Momopi?
Gyaru no momopi.
Thank you for watching!
I can't do it.
Let's go to the grill.
I'll make it into a small plate.
Small plate.
It's a cherry.
No one is watching.
Wow.
Where are you going?
Sorry.
Let's grill it.
Please subscribe to this channel.
It's done!
Wow!
Thank you so much!
Wait!
I'm shocked!
I'm surprised!
Thank you for watching!
Let's eat!
Yeah!
Please press the button.
Itadakimasu!
They prepared peach juice for us.
Thank you so much.
Cheers!
Cheers with ice tea!
Gochisousamadesita!
The peach is amazing!
It's so good!
It's like eating the peach itself.
It's so good.
It's the size of a human.
It's finally time to eat Takeru-kun.
I'm going to eat Takeru-kun's eyes.
It's so good!
The peach goes well with the sauce.
How is it?
It's refreshing and good.
The dough is well seasoned.
So, it's different from the usual pizza
with ketchup and bacon.
It's the best.
This is really good.
It's not sweet, but the cherry jam and
peach are refreshing.
So, it's light.
But, it's good.
It looks so good.
It's the best.
I'm so happy.
Thank you.
It's good to make it and eat it by
yourself.
It's a love-hate relationship.
You can try making pizza.
Please try it.
I've been waiting for this.
It's a new menu.
It looks good.
It's made by a professional pizza
maker.
Let's eat professional pizza together.
I'm so happy.
Let's eat pizza.
Please subscribe to this channel.
Yeah
Thank you for watching.
Wow!
This is my first time to eat pizza.
It's fruity.
It's really good.
I think it's good for people who don't
like salty food.
Pizza and peach go well together.
Yes.
They go well together.
It's like a sweet.
There are other peaches.
We can't finish this.
That's right.
I want you to call Okazaki-san back.
I'm sorry.
Okazaki-san.
Okazaki-chan.
You enjoyed it.
Yes.
We have a lecture about the next peach.
What do you mean?
It's like this.
Is it about peaches?
Yes.
It's a lecture about peaches.
Let's go.
Please subscribe to this channel.
Yeah, I moved the place, and I was
guided by Mr. Okazaki with a little
peach connection, but what do you do?
It's in front of you. Actually, it's a
peach-shaped
Mr. Kokeshi.
Say Momo-chan.
But it's still not in the face.
Yes, it's like a doll.
From now on, I will have a picture
experience.
I will.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
So, the teacher of the picture
experience is Mr. Sato.
Thank you.
I'm looking forward to working with
you.
I'm going to make one of the world's
best Fukumomo-chan Kogashi.
I'm looking forward to working with
you.
I'm going to give you one more chance.
Who do you want to give this to?
If you get this right,
you can write your dream, hope, wish,
and free will.
That's what I'm writing about.
How is it?
Unique!
Really?
Delicious!
The most boring one is the safety of
the wife.
I love it.
I'm going to write it down.
Are you ready?
Yes.
So, let's get started.
First, who do you want to write to?
Yes.
One person.
I want to write to Mr. Kiginari Tohoku.
I hope you can build a sense of unity
with 9 people.
I'm not dreaming, I'm aiming for it.
It's not a dream, it's a goal.
Yes, it's a goal.
It's hard.
But it's okay.
I'm going to go next.
I put it on myself.
I'll go.
Thank you for watching this video.
Please subscribe to this channel.
I'm so nervous.
I believe in myself.
I hope everyone will be happy.
It's a little bit on your face.
I'm doing it with the tone of my voice.
So, this Fukumomo-chan we made this
time will be exhibited somewhere in
Horima-chan later.
Thank you very much.
The box is here.
Here, here, together.
I'm so happy.
I did it.
I'm happy.
Mr. Okazaki.
Thank you very much, Mr. Sato.
So far, everyone has experienced
various peaches.
Yes.
There is one more peach.
I did it.
Let's go to experience another peach.
Let's go.
We have arrived.
Yes.
Today, as you can see from this, we are
in the peach field in the season.
We are in the peach field of Mr. Goto.
Mr. Goto.
Thank you.
Nice to meet you.
Horimachi is a peach village that has
been producing peaches for 29 years in
the Tennokei and Miyake prefectures.
We always send the highest quality
peaches from Horimachi to all over the
country.
I hope you can see the peaches of Mr.
Goto's house.
Thank you, Mr. Goto.
Thank you.
I have been making peaches for about 40
years.
Wow.
There are about 12 varieties here.
As I mentioned earlier, the variety
called Akatsuki in the white area
written in red is the Akatsuki in the
100 hectares of peach area of 200
hectares in Horimachi.
So, I think it's good to think that
half of the area is Akatsuki.
It's hard to get the peaches in the
market now, but it takes about three
days to get them in your mouth, so I'm
harvesting them so that they become soft
at that time.
You can't twist them.
So, the best thing is to pull them out
vertically.
Like this.
Wow.
Splash.
Please do it.
Yes.
Is it okay?
Who will do it?
I'm glad.
I'll do it.
It takes a lot of power.
Wow.
Oh, no.
What?
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I'll do it.
Wow.
It takes a lot of power.
It does.
How is it?
It's passed.
It's good.
It's really...
One, two.
It's pretty...
It's okay.
It's cute.
It's soft.
We got them, so we'll eat them and go
home.
Please subscribe to this channel.
I'm going to eat it.
Thank you.
I'm happy.
It looks delicious.
Let's eat.
It smells so good.
I know.
It's delicious.
How is it?
It's really delicious.
It's delicious.
The taste of peach is not so sweet as
to say,
It's sweet. It's not so sweet as to
say,
It's a little bit sweet.
Hotapi.
It's mixed well.
You don't know?
Yes.
Thank you.
My dream is peach.
It's hotapi which is popular now.
The peach of hotapi is peach.
Please subscribe to my Gyo channel.
I heard there is another feature of
hotapi.
I'll ask the fairy behind me.
Fairy!
Yes?
I heard that the peach of hotapi is
peach.
I understand.
What is hota?
What? Hota?
Yes.
Let's go to the next place about the
mystery of hota.
I haven't finished eating yet. Can you
stand up a little more?
I understand.
I'm going to eat hotapi.
We have arrived.
It's pitch black.
This is called the village of the plum.
There is a signboard.
The village of the plum.
This is the hotapi that I mentioned
earlier.
I see.
I was wondering what it was.
I can see fireflies.
Fireflies?
Do you want to see?
I want to see.
I'm glad you're in Manchester.
Let's go to see fireflies.
I'm scared.
Please subscribe to this channel.
Wow, it's so beautiful!
It's so small!
It's shining!
It's so beautiful!
It's like a dream!
It's amazing!
It's so beautiful!
The next day
So...
The fireflies were very beautiful.
I'm glad.
There were a lot of fireflies.
There are more fireflies in the season.
My body is covered with fireflies.
Maybe.
There are many things to eat and see.
There are many things to see.
There are many things to see and
Kumamon will decorate the house.
I see.
I hope you will be safe.
You can enjoy the fireflies and see
what we made today.
Please come to see the fireflies.
It was fun.
It was delicious and fun.
Thank you very much.
Thank you again.
Let's say goodbye together.
Bye bye.